Let's look at some common mistakes that students
might make in the previous practice exercise about
accommodation forms.
In questions 2 and 4, if students are
not careful, they might add the year of
birth for question 2 and the word year
for question 4, which are not necessary.
Another question that students might find tricky is
question 5.
Since you can only write one word and
or a number for this exercise, there has
to be a hyphen between self and catering.
This is the correct way to spell this
word, since it is a compound word.
So, how can we avoid making these mistakes in
form filling?
First, we should be well prepared for everything
before listening.
You have to read the requirement carefully to
not exceed the word limit.
Making predictions is really important.
In this step, it is necessary to predict
some paraphrases so that you can listen in
an attentive and active way.
By doing that, you can find the answers
faster, and this also helps to improve your
vocabulary.
When making predictions for each blank, you need
to base on their grammatical structures and the
context of conversations.
After listening, you have to check your answers
to avoid unnecessary mistakes.
Next, you will practice listening for details to
avoid making common spelling mistakes in form filling.
See you soon!